typingagent.com 2018-05-11

# Untitled Document

At Typing Agent, (located in Edmonds, WA 98020) we are acutely aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your and your students’ privacy. We keep all user and account information, including free trial registrants and licensed users, strictly private and confidential. We only use the information we collect to process orders and to provide product technical support.

Your email address will serve as your login username. Your email address may be used to send a confirmation email at registration, as well as information and updates to the programs. We may use the email address as an additional means of communicating with you about the Programs and Typing Agent, including notifying you of updates to the Web Site or its related policies.

If you choose to provide us with personal information by ordering our products, sending an email, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information to fulfill your order, respond to your message or to help us provide you with information or material that you request.

Typing Agent will not sell, trade, rent or publish customer data to any advertisers, or third parties, other than for purposes of processing a transaction and providing direct product support for Typing Agent and its subsidiaries. Student data, most specifically is not used, accessed, or shared with any third party and is kept strictly confidential by Typing Agent LLC.

**Details of Transactions:**  
All payment details you provide during online transactions are processed by a secure third party and transaction details are NOT retained or kept on our secure servers.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
Any customer information received by Typing Agent directly, from its authorized resellers or from its online registration service providers (see below) is hosted on a secured server. Firewalls, passwords, and encryption technology protect the information about our customers that we collect and securely store.

Typing Agent may release customer information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our member agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Typing Agent our customers or others. We will not send you unsolicited third-party promotional emails.

Except for the circumstances set forth in the previous paragraph, we will not knowingly distribute customer information to be used in mailing lists, surveys, or any other purpose other than what is required to perform our services.

**How does Typing Agent Protect Student Data:**  
Student information collected is limited to what is required for the teachers to identify the students in their class. This includes: username, password, name and grade. Only this information is stored securely online for students. Furthermore, Typing Agent understands the importance of protecting student data and information. Personal student information is NOT required to be able to use the Typing Agent program. In light of this, the only parties that have access to student information will be: District Administrators, Teachers and Typing Agent support and their respective resellers and this is strictly limited to customer or technical support purposes only.

In the event of an unauthorized disclosure of a student’s records, Typing Agent will report to the master account holder of the affected school or district in an app communication and email as to the depth and breadth of the data breach and provide messaging that can be shared with the parents of legal guardians of the students.

In addition, following a one year period of time after a school or districts account expires, student identifying records will be deleted from our database archives and no longer available for use by Typing Agent. For reporting purposes, an overview report of the school or districts progress (excluding student identifying data) will be retained for analytical purposes. Prior to this one year period and during the duration of the Typing Agent subscription, students, parents, teachers, and administrators can print a report of an overview of the work that the student accomplished while on the program.

Please note: student passwords are visible to teachers and administrators of the program. Best practice is NOT to have students use common passwords or passwords they use elsewhere.

Typing Agent shall take actions to ensure the security and confidentiality of all students, including but not limited to designating and training responsible individuals on ensuring the security and confidentiality of student records, by securely storing student data behind a 256 Bit secure SSL certificate. Schools and districts have control over how they would prefer to identify their students within the Typing Agent program. In addition, only Typing Agent support staff, teachers or school administrators have access to student records. The minimal student identification information that is required to use Typing Agent, is a username. Personal student contact information is NOT required to be able to use the Typing Agent program. Typing Agent does allow schools or districts to enable third party single sign on applications. Schools and Districts who elect to do this are responsible for managing their student privacy relationship with those third party entities.

Parents, legal guardians, or eligible may review personally identifiable information in the student’s records and correct erroneous information by contacting their teacher or school administrators directly.

**What about Cookies?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Typing Agent's cookies are used only to store your geographical region/language settings, which enables us to always show correct ordering information to you. These cookies do not store sensitive data and they do not identify any specific customer traits.

**Links to Other Sites:**  
Typing Agent's web site may provide links to other Internet sites that we think may be of interest to our customers. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

The privacy policies of our service providers or linked sites are the responsibility of each provider and site and Typing Agent has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each provider for specific information. Typing Agent cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

All our order processing partners respect the privacy of our customers and security is their number one priority. Any and all information collected through their systems is treated with the utmost care.

Typing Agent may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will notify you by email regarding any material changes to our privacy and security practices.

As Typing Agent continues to develop its business, it may sell some or all of its assets. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. An acquiring company would be required to protect all information that Typing Agent collects from users of our website and programs in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

In the event of a future sale or merger of the company, all future companies will be required to abide by the same high Privacy Policy standards that Typing Agent is committing to uphold.

**CIPA Considerations**  
Typing Agent hereby warrants that the creative content provided on this Site complies by with the Children's Internet Protection Act (CIPA).

If you have any questions about your privacy or security measures at Typing Agent, please contact us at:

**Company Headquarters:**  
Typing Agent, LLC  
51 West Dayton, Suite #302  
Edmonds, WA 98020  
Tel: 425.880.2500  
Fax: 1.866.271.9646  
Email: [support@tyingagent.com](mailto:support@tyingagent.com)  
This website is © 2015 by Typing Agent. All rights reserved
